and will punish man.
"'and you ate'
and the word of God.
30 years and 800 years
ויהיהו כל ימי שאת 12 שנה ו-900 שנה וימות ויחי אנוש 90 שנה ויולד את קנאן ויחי אנוש אחרי הולידו את קנאן 15 שנה ו-800 שנה ויולד בנים ובנות ויהיו כל ימי אנוש 5 שנים ו-900 שנה וימות ויחי קנאן 70 שנה ויולד את מהל על אל ויוםות וימות ויחי אנוש 90 שנה ויולד את קנאן ויחי אנוש אחרי הולידו את קנאן 15 שנה ו-800 שנה ויולד בנים ובנות ויהיו כל ימי אנוש 5 שנים ו-900 שנה וימות ויחי קנאן 70 שנה ויולד את מהל על אל ויוםות ויחי קנאן 70 שנה ויולד את מהל על אל ויוםות ויוםות ויוםות ויוםות ויוםות ויוםות ויוםות ויוםות ויוםות ויוםות ויוםות ויוםות ויוםות ויוםות ויוםות ויוםות ויוםות ויוםות ויוםות ויוםות ויוםות ויוםות ויוםות ויוםות ויוםות ויוםות ויוםות ויוםות ויוםות ויוםות ויוםות ויוםות ויוםות ויוםות ויוםות ויוםות ויוםות ויוםות ויוםות ויוםות ויוםות ויוםות ויוםות ויוםות ויוםות ויוםות ויוםות ויוםות ויוםות ויוםות ויוםות ויוםות ויוםות ויוםות וי and will live in Canaan
את כל ירק העשב לאוכלה.
"'For the tree is good for food "'And you have given it to the eyes "'And the tree is nice to eat "'And you will take from its fruit and eat "'And you will eat from its fruit "'And you will eat from its fruit "'And you will eat from its fruit "'And you will eat from its fruit "'And you will eat from its fruit "'And you will eat from its fruit "'And you will eat from its fruit "'And you will eat from its fruit "'And you will eat from its fruit "'And you will eat from its fruit "'And you will eat from its fruit "'And you will eat from its fruit "'And you will eat from its fruit "'And you will eat from its fruit "'And you will eat from its fruit "'And you will eat from its fruit "'And you will eat from its fruit "'And you will eat from its fruit "'And you will eat from its fruit "'And you will eat from its fruit "'And you will eat from its fruit "'And you will eat from its fruit "'And you will eat from its fruit "'And you will eat from its fruit "'And you will eat from its fruit "'And you will eat from its fruit "'And you will eat from its fruit "'And you will eat from its fruit "'And you will eat from its fruit "'And you will eat from its fruit "'And you will eat from its fruit "'And you will eat from its fruit "'And you will eat from its fruit "'And you will eat from its fruit "'And you will eat from its fruit "'And you will eat from its fruit "'And you will eat from its fruit "'And you will eat from its fruit "'And you will eat from its fruit "'And you will eat from its fruit "'And you will eat from its fruit "'And you will eat from its fruit "'And you will eat from its fruit "'And you will eat from its fruit "'And you will eat from its fruit "'And you will eat from its fruit "'And you will eat from its fruit "'And you will eat from its fruit "'And you will eat from its fruit "'And you will eat from its fruit "'And you will eat from its own, "'and will give to the woman, mother, and will eat "'and will open the eyes of the others "'and will know that they are poor "'and will speak on the tongue "'and will make for them the fasts "'and will hear the voice of the Lord, God "'going in the garden to the spirit of the day "'and will hide I'm
For from where did you take?
and there will be...
and says,
and the Lord said,
V'y'olet, et l'amech, v'y'ch'im, et'us'elach,
והאדם ידע את חווה אשתו.
From blood to blood, from dusk to dawn,
and she will build a city, and will call the city by its name,
65 years and 300 years
and will strive and God will make
The rain of the evening is pouring down from its right,
and he fought with his wife, and they were one flesh,
לא מצא האזר כנגדו ויפאל.
"'and the water that is above the rock,
"'And he said to the woman,
Zachar un'keva ber'am, v'yivar'ech otam, v'yikra'et shemam adam,
The tree of the garden, the tree of knowledge,
The light will shine, and if not, it will be a fire, a fire of fire.
and the earth will be shaken from the earth and all the faces of the earth will be cast down.
"'Do not eat from us, do not touch it, you will die.'
From the earth, the song of the red earth
The song of Asa, the king of the seven days,
260 years and 900 years and days
The earth is full of your forelocks, and the clouds are inside us, all the days of your life.
God, earth and sky, and all the vastness of the field,
וכל יצר מחשבות ליבו רק רע כל היום.
In the beginning God created the sky and the earth,
Nefesh, Chaya, Hu, Shemot.
Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er,
The song
and will give birth to a son and will call his name Noah, the son of Mor.
Zoray Ya'zara' L'cheh Me'yeh L'och'lah
And also, after that, the song will come,
The garden in Eden, before, and the man who created and created will be placed there.
"'and the Lord will remove your sin "'and He will wipe it off "'
Yikavu amayim,
I didn't know the guard was my brother, my brother, and Yomer made fun of me.
500 years old, and the boy named Noah, Ham and Japheth.
ואתה הרור עטה מן הדמה שפצת את פיה לקחת את דמעךיך מידיך כי תאוות את הדמה לא תוספת את כוחך לך נע ונד תהיה בארץ ויומר קניין ה' גדול עבוני מן נשמה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעה ונעל ונעל ונעל ונעל ונעל ונעל ונ The day you cast me away
And the river came out of the cave to wash away the garden, and from there it separated and became four heads, one of them being Pishon.
and you, son of the messenger, will be taken away from the living tree,
To man and his wife, with golden robes, and they will dress them.
"'Lachen, kol horeg Kain, שבעתיים יוקם, ויעשם ה' לכאין, אות לבלתי הכות אותו, כל מוצאו.
אלוהים ויומר להם אלוהים פירו ורווו ומלאו את הארץ וחבשוها.
וייקח לו למך שתי נשים, שם האחת עדה ושם השנית צילה, ותלד עדה את יבל, הוא היה אבי.
I'll make no harm against him, and I'll create God, God, from the earth, all life, the field,
ויקדש אותו כיבו שבת מכל מלכתו אשר ברא אלוהים לעשות.
And there is a way,
"'and the man said,
Here, I gave you
And the boy, sons and daughters
after his holiday, the day of the God.
And he stole me penny Adonai Elohim beto
וייכן ויר אלוהים את כל שרעשר.
For you have turned, and you have turned again.
every human day that lives 900 years and 30 years and will die and will be born...
My Lord God,
''No one will judge the spirit of man in the world,
a'ch'ar'e, hol'id'oh, et'lemech,
ותהר ותלד את קין ותומר, קניתי איש.
And they will be, every day, up in heaven
For I have rested, for I am thirsty,
"'The woman who gave me food,
and will build a kindergarten, and will give birth to a child,
and the God was taken away from us
the life of the earth
and the fire is making a fire,
and their eyes were blue, the man and his wife,
to the snake,
40 years and 800 more years,
ה' אלוהים, תרדמה על האדם וישן,
שתיים, ו-שמונים, שנה, ו-שבעה מאות שנה,
"'Never! For God said,
B'yom hee-baar'e-am, v'y'ch'ee adam, 30'u-ma'at sh'anah,
"'and the fire, and the God of the rock,
good and evil cannot eat from it,
And you will be the one who will be burned, and you will be the one who will be destroyed.
from the beginning to the end,
95 years and 800 years
"'And the snake said to the woman, "'You will not die, you will die,
And the Lord of God will create man from the earth and he will spit on his face the smell of life.
And it will be ready for the day of your birth, Noah
and will live for 560 years
from all the kings of Asa.
And the roots and the branches will be proud of you, and you ate the stone of the field,
may the earth be full, and all the vastness of the field,
וינחם אדוניי כי עשה את האדם בארץ, ויתעצב אל ליבו.
Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er,
and the earth was his and his, and darkness on the face of darkness,
Vayn'kra, Ha-Adam, Shemot.
Its a gun Vickra
And my soul is in my Lord's eyes.
and children, sons and daughters,
''for he is dead and gone,
and will build a kindergarten for Airan and Airad,
as it is pouring from its right,
And the name of man is the name of his wife, Hava.
that on the water's surface
This
U'l'chol Chayat Ha'aretz U'l'chol R'of Ha'Shamayim
Between the gods, to the human beings, and they will be born.
ו'י'ול, את בנים, ובנות, ויהיהו כל ימי מתושלך,
My Lord, God, from the earth, all the wood, nice to see and good to eat,
"'and man will say "'You heard the voice of your wife "'and you will eat from the tree "'
"'she gave me from the wood and food,
And they will die and be resurrected
because on the day it eats from it, death will die.
Mithat ha-shamayim,
and they were not crushed.
And he called the people, mostly the people of the earth,
"'Never eat from the tree of the garden.'
Today, from above the face of the earth, I will hide your face
and the Lord is calling,
for you have done this,
He is the one who surrounds all the lands of the Chavilah, the song is there.
and will eat and live forever, and God will send him,
and they will be every day in Canaan.
Adonai Elohim El hadam
And Yomer will cry, Elhevel, my brother, and he will throw them into the field.
And he will say, My Lord God,
''and 120 years of his days are gone.''
may it be full, for God will not delay.
את אלוהי ותוסף ללדת את אחיו, את האבל.
"'for God knows, "'for on the day you will eat from us,
V'y'ol'et bid'mu-to'k'e-tsalmoh, v'y'kra'et shemo'o-sh'et,
and will give birth to the child
"'and the sky, and the evening, and the morning,
to its right and the earth to its left
because God took him away
5 years and a few years and will give birth to a human and will be born...
a child born from the life of God, and from the life of God,
וייקח אחת מצלעותיו, ויסגור בשר תחתנה, וייבן.
Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er,
62 years and 100 years
for the near ones and the road of the future,
and your father's anger is inside the flesh.
10 years and 900 more years,
590 years and 500 years
El makom echad,
They, the heroes,
For she was alive, they are all alive.
Vaya merlo I yeka
And the snake was blue from all the life of the field,
and it is evening, and it is morning,
תשע, ו-שישים, שנה, ו-תשע מאות שנה,
"'and the Lord said,
you, the enemy,
V'te'e ra'e ha-yabashah,
"'And the woman said to the snake,
and the daughters were born to them.
Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er,
and they will die and will live on the God.
And Jacob will cry, Elhevel, my brother, and he will kill him.
"'God, what have you done to the woman?'
all the darkness of the fields of the field,
And I will be a slave in the land
And the boy, Hanukkah
And there will be children, sons and daughters
V'y'ee-yoo y'me-adam, a'ch'ar'e ho-le-do'et-sh'et,
and all the darkness of the earth to its right
The song from the world, the people of God,
a child born from the dead of God, and from the dead of God,
of all the beasts,
Vay'he'chen,
Vaya Oh Oh mirror
"'From the branch of the garden, eat from the branch of the tree.'"
And today, says the Lord God,
the Lord of the gods, from the Garden of Eden,
And he will be resurrected
And there will be all the days of your birth
And God showed the daughters of man,
5 years and 60 more years,
Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er,
Vay'kra'a Elohim,
to the two kinds
the rest on the face of all the land,
After the holiday, Hanukkah
"'And you said,
and of all the life of the field,
770 years and 700 years
La-yabashah ha-eretz,
Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er,
the day of the people,
and a child will be born and will live on the God.
And if you find me, you will kill me
and all the waves
and the Lord will come as a light
and all the fire,
"'The woman, the snake,
800 years and the boy, sons and daughters
U'l-mikve' ha-mayim,
Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er, Yom-er,
on your throat you walk,
he took to the two kinds
It call aka shama T bagan
The song is in the garden.
Ka'ra'a yamim,
and the God's tree
for good